Preliminary Guide to the AIDS Action Foundation records, 1984-2006 MS2212
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- History, 1984-2005; Series 2; 5.75 Linear Feet
  - Outgoing grant projects [What Works Guide, Adherence Manuals, Conference Abstracts], 2001; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - What Works in HIV Prevention for Incarcerated Populations, 2001; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Syring access, 2001; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - World Map Project, 2001; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - planning documents, 2001; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - AIDS Action Foundation, 2001 November 17; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - AIDS Action documents, 2002; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - State Fact Sheets, 2002; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Research Rapid Test/CUA, 2002; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Adolescents and HIV/AIDS, 2002; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Innovation for Adolescent Girls and HIV/AIDS conference, 2002 September 10; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - AIDS Action correspondence, 2002; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - HIV prevention works draft, 2002 April; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Ballot and nominations, 2002; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Ballot and nominations, 2002 January; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Management, 2002; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Board and Committee lists, 2002; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Mission Statement, 2002; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Officer ballots, 2002; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - AIDS Action work plan, 2002; Series 2 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Global Authorization, 2003; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Stigma of AIDS, 2002-2003; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Sample AIDS Action publications, 2002-2005, undated; Series 2 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - New board member apps, 2003 October; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Balm of Gilead visit, 2003; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - CDLS Abstract [Community Planning Leadership Summit], 2003; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Speaking engagements, 2003; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Hearing dispatches in healthcare, 2003; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Commitment forms, 2003; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - MayaTech speech, 2003; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Thank Yous, 2003; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Africa, 2003; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Community Outreach Group, 2003; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - AIDS Action Policy Initiatives, 2003; Series 2 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - AIDS Action Foundation 8th Annual Dinner, Los Angeles, 2003; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - AIDs Action Foundation financial records, 2003-2004; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Factsheets (Kaiser), 2003-2004; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Teens and Sex, 2004; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Names reception, 2004; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Vice Presidential debate, 2004; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - NGO status, 2004; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - US Conference on AIDS, 2004; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - All Staff Meetings, 2004-2006; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Deputy Director meetings, 2004-2005; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Board dues, 2005; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - AIDS Watch, 2005; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - World AIDS Day, 2005; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ready Set Go/ Institution, 2005; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AIDS Action Council work plan draft, 2005; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Membership dues survey, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - AIDS Action Council roster and terms, undated; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - January meeting rsvps, undated; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - AIDS Action Foundation resumes, undated; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - AIDS Action History Council and Foundation, undated; Series 2 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Media Services program, undated; Series 2 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Media Services surveys, undated; Series 2 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Newsletter information, undated; Series 2 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Newsletter pictures and captions, undated; Series 2 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper articles, undated; Series 2 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - AIDS Action Foundation by-laws, undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - AIDS Action Council resumes, undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - AIDs Action Council by-laws and committee functions, undated; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Advisory Panel Report, undated; Series 2 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Daniel [Zingale] materials, undated; Series 2 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey, undated; Series 2 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 151-200, undated; Series 2 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 201-250 [1/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 201-250 [2/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 201-250 [3/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 251-300 [1/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 251-300 [2/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 251-300 [3/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 1-50 [1/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 1-50 [2/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 1-50 [3/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 301-350 [1/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 301-350 [2/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 301-350 [3/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 101-150 [1/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 101-150 [2/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 101-150 [3/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 51-100 [1/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 51-100 [2/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 51-100 [3/3], undated; Series 2 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 401-431 [1/2], undated; Series 2 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 401-431 [2/2], undated; Series 2 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 352-380, undated; Series 2 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 381-400, undated; Series 2 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 374-375, unnumbered, undated; Series 2 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey 432-437, 351, undated; Series 2 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey [1/2], undated; Series 2 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    These surveys were not calculated because they came in after the surveys were sent to data analysis.
  - AIDS Action HIV Prevention Survey [2/2], undated; Series 2 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Board, undated; Series 2 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - AIDS Action data, undated; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - By-laws, undated; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Benefits of membership, undated; Series 2 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - What Works for Gay Men (binder) [1/2], undated; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - What Works for Gay Men (binder) [2/2], undated; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Baltimore Pediatric HIV Program [Debbie Rock], undated; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Fact Sheet resources, undated; Series 2 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - HIV and Service members, undated; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Institute of Medicine, undated; Series 2 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - "Special AIDS", undated; Series 2 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Zamora [Pedro], undated; Series 2 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Cuba, undated; Series 2 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Staff/Budget, undated; Series 2 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Website e-march, undated; Series 2 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Prevention, undated; Series 2 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Overhaul, undated; Series 2 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Medicaid, undated; Series 2 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Housing, undated; Series 2 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - FDA reform, undated; Series 2 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Drug Success, undated; Series 2 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Blinded babies, undated; Series 2 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Vaccines, undated; Series 2 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Rape Initiative, undated; Series 2 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Building, undated; Series 2 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - [David] Satcher, undated; Series 2 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Quarterly, undated; Series 2 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Zingale media kit, undated; Series 2 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Celebrities, undated; Series 2 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Mandatory testing of pregnant women, undated; Series 2 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Desario letter to Shalala, undated; Series 2 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Desario Case, undated; Series 2 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Wisconsin AIDS Response network, undated; Series 2 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Chandler Burr, undated; Series 2 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - HIV/AIDS marketing samples [1/2], undated; Series 2 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - HIV/AIDS marketing samples [2/2], undated; Series 2 (Box 73, Folder 15)
- National Organizations Responding to AIDS (NORA), 1987-2005; Series 3; 3.5 item(s)
  Historical note
  Founded in 1987 by the AIDS Action Council and other organizations, the National Organizations Responding to AIDS (NORA) is dedicated to fighting for a fair and effective Federal response to AIDS. NORA's efforts have included briefings for the Senate and House on the Ryan White CARE Act and yearly budget recommendations for AIDS programs to Congress. The members of NORA work towards passing critical legislative efforts including reauthorizing the Ryan White CARE Act, opposing mandatory testing proposals, and protecting the needs of people with AIDS in the debates over Medicaid and other Federal health programs. Led by a nine-member executive committee, NORA's membership includes more than 150 organizations.
  This series contains working documents of NORA including correspondence, memos, meeting materials, dues, publications, executive committee records, and appropriations documents. These records date from 1987-2005.
  - NORA and AIDS Action Council, 1987-1989; Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - NORA publications, 1989-2001; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - NORA publications, 1992-2002; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - NORA prevention condom working group, 1992; Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - NORA Substance Abuse task force, 1993; Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - NORA membership, 1993; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - NORA dues, 1993; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - NORA dues process, 1994; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - NORA testimony, 1994; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - NORA information, 1994; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - NORA information, 1993; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - NORA information, 1993; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - NORA working groups, 1995; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - NORA sign-on letters, 1995; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - NORA memos, 1995; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - NORA meetings, 1995; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - NORA membership information, 1995; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - NORA testimony, 1995; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - NORA Executive Committee memos, 1995; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - NORA Executive Committee meetings, 1995; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - NORA organization, 1995; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - NORA White Policy Paper, Circa 1995; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - NORA meeting, 1995 May 8; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - FY95 NORA Testimony, 1995; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Old NORA, 1997-1998; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - NORA neg. amend. Letters, 1997-1999; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - NORA executive committee elections, 1999 November; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - NORA faxes sent, 1999; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - NORA memos, 1996; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - NORA membership information, 1996; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - NORA sign-on letters, 1996; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - NORA meetings, 1996; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - NORA Executive Committee memos, 1996; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - NORA Executive Committee letters, 1996; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - NORA other correspondence, 1996; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - NORA Executive Committee meetings, 1996; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - NORA appropriations documents, 1997; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - NORA appropriations documents, 1998; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - NORA appropriations documents FY 98, 1998-1999; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - NORA Executive Committee meeting, 1998 June 16; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - NORA Executive Committee, 1999; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - NORA dues paid invoices, 1999; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - NORA appropriations documents, 2000; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - NORA contact information, 2000; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - NORA FY 2001 Approps doc., 2000; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - NORA WG sign-ons, 2000 June 9; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - NORA letters and info, 2000; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - NORA information, 2002; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Policy Agenda, 2002-2003; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - NORA Dues, 2002; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - NORA working groups, 2003; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - NORA information, 2003; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - NORA coalition, 2003; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - NORA Executive Committee, 2003; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - NORA Dues, 2003; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - NORA meeting, 2004; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - NORA Executive Committee, 2004; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - NORA coalition, 2004; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Internal NORA, 2004; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - NORA Executive Committee, 2005; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - NORA Coalition, 2005; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - NORA information, 2005; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - NORA Workgroup workspace, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - NORA Contact sheets, undated; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - NORA Budget, undated; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - NORA Research Working Group, undated; Series 3 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - NORA International Issues WG, undated; Series 3 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - NORA Incarcerated population WG, undated; Series 3 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - NORA Youth Working Group, undated; Series 3 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - NORA Appropriations WG, undated; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - NORA Testing and Prevention WG, undated; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - NORA RWCR meeting, 1999; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - NORA RWCA reauthorization WG, undated; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - NORA letters and information, undated; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - NORA women and AIDS task force, undated; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - NORA RWCA briefing, undated; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - NORA RWCA meetings, undated; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - NORA restructuring, undated; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - NORA procedures, undated; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - NORA fact book, undated; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - NORA care task force, undated; Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - NORA T.F. Co-chairs, undated; Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - NORA Civil Rights task force, undated; Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - NORA Housing task force, undated; Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - NORA Pediatrics task force, undated; Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - NORA RW Task Force, undated; Series 3 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - RW NORA memos, undated; Series 3 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Ryan White Care Act and Ryan White Foundation, 1990-2005; Series 4; 7.5 Linear Feet
  Organized into 3 subseries: Ryan White Care Act Reauthorization, Legislation, and Ryan White Foundation.
  This series contains correspondence, drawings, legislation, appropriation data, memos, and reports related to the work to reauthorize the Ryan White Care Act and also the work of the Ryan White Foundation. This material dates from 1990-2005.
  - Ryan White Care Act Reauthorization, 1990-2005; Series 4 Subseries 1
    The Ryan White Care Act is the United States's largest federally funded program for people living with HIV/AIDS. The act sought funding to improve availability of care for low-income, uninsured and under-insured victims of AIDS and their families. The Ryan White Care Act was reauthorized in 1996, 2000 and 2006.
    - RW Reauthorization of 1990, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Ryan White Reauthorization, 1994; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - RW Reauth testimony, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - RW Reauthorization 1995, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Reauthorization, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Reauth. Sign on, 2000 May; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Ryan White 2000 authorization, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Reauthorization update, 2002-2005; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - RWCA reauthorization and appropriations planning and strategy session, 2004; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - RWCA reauthorization and appropriations planning and strategy session, 2004; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - RWCA reauthorization and appropriations planning and strategy session, 2004 January 29; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - RWCA reauthorization and appropriations planning and strategy session, 2004 January 29; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - RWCA reauthorization documents, 2004-2006; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - RWCA reauthorization documents, 2004-2006; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - RWCA reauthorization documents, 2004-2006; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - RWCA reauthorization documents, 2004-2006; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - RWCA reauthorization documents, 2004-2006; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - RWCA reauthorization documents, 2004-2006; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - RWCA reauthorization documents, 2004-2006; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Board Reauth Subcommittee, 2005; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Reauthorization meeting [1/2], 2005; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Reauthorization meeting [2/2], 2005; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Board Ryan White Act, 2005; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Reauthorization update, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Reauthorization talking points, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - RW Reauthorization questionnaire, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Care Act Reauthorization summary, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Reauthorization R White (AAC), undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - R White Reauthorization letters, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Testimony Margaret Hamburg Reauthorization of the RW Care Act, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - ADAP working group RWCA Reauth, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - CARE Act Reauthorization Task Force recommendations, undated; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Legislation for the act, 1990-1999; Series 4 Subseries 2
    In August 1990, Congress passed the Ryan White Comprehensive AIDS Resources Emergency (CARE) Act to improve the quality and availability of care for people living with HIV/AIDS and their families. The CARE Act has four titles of funding for HIV/AIDS-related services: Title I: Emergency relief grants program for cities and counties that are disproportionately affected by the HIV/AIDS epidemic. Title II: Care grants for states. Title III: Funding for early intervention services. Title IV: Funding for pediatric care and research.
    - RW Comprehensive AIDS Resources Emergency Act of 1990, Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Funding RW Title I, 1994-1995; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Funding Ryan White Title II, 1994-1996; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Funding Ryan White Title IV, 1994-1996; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Summary report Ryan White Title I baseline data year 1, 1994 August; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Testimony of Doug Nelson Hearing related to the Ryan White Care Act, 1995 February 22; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - RW H.R. 1872 RW Care Act ammendments, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - S. 641 RW Reauth Act of 95 Title IV, 1995; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Funding Ryan White Title IIIB, 1995-1996; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Funding Ryan White Title I, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Funding Dental FY96, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - FY 96 Ryan White Title IV Grantees, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - RW Care Act Amendments of 1996, Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - RW Amendments, 1996; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Ryan White AIDS programs appropriations, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Title IV FY97, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - RW Title V SPNS, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - RW Title II $$$$'s, 1997-1998; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - FY 99 Requests, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Title I Services, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Title IIIb Coalition position paper, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - S.641 Ryan White, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - HR 1872 Ryan White, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Ryan White House Bill, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - R White Grant Awards I and II, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - RW FY 96 legislative proposals, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Ryan White Title IV awards, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - S.641 Report HR 187, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - HRSA Ryan White comments, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - Ryan White bills (CR), undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Neg. amendment CARE Act $ to other diseases, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - RW Title II $$$$'s, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Ryan White GAO title II, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Title II '95 $$$, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - RWCA - bill, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - RW FY 98 app. Guidance for states Title II HIV Care Grant Program, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - FY 98 ADAP/RW Care Act, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - RW: FY 98 Grant app. Guidelines Title I HIV Emergency relief, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Testimony by David Ellingsworth, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Testimony - Victoria Sharp, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Testimony: Ryan White, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Ryan White Title II grants to states, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Ryan White Neg Amendments, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Ryan White Title IV, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Ryan White package, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Ryan White Title IIIB, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Ryan White Title IV, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 2)